♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA HAVE MYSELF
A TIME ♪
♪ FRIENDLY FACES
EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ HUMBLE FOLKS
WITHOUT TEMPTATION ♪
♪ GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA LEAVE
MY WOE'S BEHIND ♪
♪ AMPLE PARKING
DAY OR NIGHT ♪
♪ PEOPLE SHOUTING
"HOWDY NEIGHBOR" ♪
♪ HEADED ON
UP TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA SEE IF
I CAN'T UNWIND ♪
( mumbling )
♪ SO COME ON DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ AND MEET SOME
FRIENDS OF MINE ♪
HEY STAN, WHERE'D YOU
GET THAT BLACK EYE?
NOTHING,
I MEAN NOWHERE.
YOUR SISTER
BEAT YOU UP AGAIN?
NO!
YOUR SISTER
KICKED YOUR ASS!
SHE'S PISSED OFF 'CAUSE SHE GOT
HEADGEAR AT THE DENTIST.
SHE'S TAKING IT
OUT ON ME.
BUT THAT SUCKS YOU GET YOUR
BUTT KICKED BY A GIRL, STAN.
I WOULD NEVER
LET A WOMAN KICK MY ASS.
IF SHE TRIED ANYTHING,
I'D BE LIKE,
"YOU GET YOUR BITCH-ASS
BACK IN THE KITCHEN
AND MAKE ME
SOME PIE!"
MY PARENTS DON'T EVEN BELIEVE
THAT SHE BEATS ME UP.
THEY THINK SHE'S ALL
INNOCENT AND SWEET.
BUT I KNOW THAT
SHE'S AN EVIL BITCH.
BE A MAN, STAN,
JUST SAY, "HEY WOMAN
YOU SHUT YOUR MOUTH
AND MAKE BABIES!"
HEY KYLE, WHAT'S THAT
ELEPHANT DOING?
YOU MEAN
THIS ONE?
HE'S MY NEW
PET ELEPHANT.
WHERE'D YOU GET
A PET ELEPHANT?
I GOT IT MAIL ORDER
FROM AFRICA.
THE AD SAID IT WOULD
TAKE FOUR TO SIX WEEKS,
BUT IT ONLY
TOOK THREE!
WOW,
THAT'S COOL!
NO, IT'S NOT COOL!
MY MOM WON'T LET ME
KEEP HIM IN THE HOUSE!
SHE SAYS
HE'S TOO BIG
AND THAT HIS POOP
IS BIGGER THAN OUR COUCH.
THAT'S WHY MY MOM GOT ME
A POT-BELLIED PIG,
'CAUSE ITS
POOP IS SMALL.
( mumbling )
YEAH, BUT PIGS AREN'T
SMART LIKE ELEPHANTS.
HEY!
WAIT A MINUTE,
WHAT IS THAT THING?!
THIS IS THE NEW
RETARDED KID.
OH, I'M SORRY
LITTLE GIRL.
BUT YOU STILL
CAN'T GET ON!
YOU HAVE TO TAKE
THE SPECIAL-ED BUS!
DUH!
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE NOT
WELCOME ANYWHERE, ELEPHANT.
SEE YA!
IF A WOMAN
GAVE ME CRAP,
I'D SAY,
"YOU GO DO MY LAUNDRY!"
SIT DOWN, KID!
YES, MA'AM.
AND NOW CHILDREN,
OUR FRIEND MR. HAT,
IS GOING TO TELL US ALL ABOUT
GENETIC ENGINEERING.
THAT'S RIGHT,
MR. GARRISON.
GENETIC ENGINEERING IS
AN EXCITING NEW SCIENCE.
YOU CAN SPLICE THE DNA
FROM SOME ANIMALS
AND MAKE
THEM BETTER.
MR. GARRISON?
YES, KYLE.
WITH GENETIC
ENGINEERING,
CAN YOU MAKE
AN ELEPHANT SMALLER?
WELL, YES,
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD.
YOU COULD SPLICE ELEPHANT GENES
WITH A DOG OR CAT
OR POT-BELLIED PIG GENES.
THAT'S IT!
I'M GONNA COMBINE MY ELEPHANT
WITH A POT-BELLIED PIG
AND MAKE POT-BELLIED
ELEPHANTS.
THEY'D BE SMART
LIKE ELEPHANTS,
BUT SMALL LIKE PIGS.
THAT'D BE COOL!
I'D WANT A
POT-BELLIED ELEPHANT.
YES, I'LL PAY
$50 FOR ONE.
THAT'S STUPID.
SHUT UP!
WE COULD GENETICAL ENGINEER
ANYTHING WE WANT.
I BET I COULD CLONE
A HUMAN BEING
BEFORE YOU CROSSBREED
AN ELEPHANT AND A PIG.
I'LL BET
YOU CAN'T!
WATCH ME,
PLEBEIAN.
WELL, SPANK MY ASS
AND CALL ME CHARLIE.
ISN'T THIS EXCITING?
TWO "A+" STUDENTS
IN A CLONING WAR.
YES, MR. GARRISON.
GENETIC ENGINEERING
LET'S US CORRECT
GOD'S HORRIBLE,
HORRIBLE MISTAKES,
LIKE GERMAN PEOPLE.
YOU BOYS MIGHT WANNA VISIT
THE GENETIC ENGINEERING RANCH
OUTSIDE OF TOWN
FOR SOME HELP.
AND YOU COULD
BOTH USE THIS
FOR YOUR SCIENCE FAIR
PROJECTS NEXT MONTH.
GENETIC
ENGINEERING RANCH?
SWEET!
WAIT, WAIT,
WE STILL NEED A PIG.
WE COULD USE
CARTMAN'S PIGS.
YOU LEAVE FLUFFY
OUT OF THIS!
WE'RE NOT GONNA
HURT HER.
WE JUST NEED
SOME OF HER BLOOD.
YOU'RE NOT USING
ANY OF FLUFFY'S BLOOD!
I'LL KICK YOU
IN THE NUTS!
KYLE, KYLE, NO!
STANLEY, CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
OKAY.
I COULDN'T HELP NOTICE
THAT BLACK EYE.
ARE THERE
PROBLEMS AT HOME?
YES.
OH, DEAR.
HERE STANLEY,
SIT DOWN,
HAVE SOME COCOA,
AND TELL YOUR FRIEND
MR. HAT ALL ABOUT IT.
I'M YOUR FRIEND,
MR. HAT, STAN,
YOU CAN
TELL ME ANYTHING.
NOW WHO HIT YOU?
IS IT YOUR FATHER
OR YOUR MOTHER?
NEITHER,
IT'S MY SISTER.
YOUR SISTER?!
OH FOR PETE'S SAKE,
DON'T BE SUCH A LITTLE WUS!
STOP WASTING MR. HAT'S TIME
WITH PANSY LITTLE FU-FU PROBLEMS
AND GIVE ME BACK
MY COCOA!
HEY!
HI, SHELLY.
ARE YOU LOOKING
AT MY HEADGEAR?
HEADGEAR,
WHAT HEADGEAR?
ARE YOU LOOKING
AT MY HEADGEAR?!
GOSH, I DIDN'T
REALLY NOTICE.
YOU LITTLE LIAR!
NO, I THINK
IT LOOKS TERRIFIC!
IT MATCHES YOUR--
AAH...!
READY TO GO,
STAN?
GO WHERE?
TO THE GENETICAL
ENGINEERING RANCH.
WE GOT
CARTMAN'S PIG,
SO WE CAN SPLICE ITS GENES
WITH MY ELEPHANT.
NOBODY'S SPLICING
NOTHING FROM FLUFFY!
( Shelly )
I SWEAR I'M GONNA
KILL YOU, STAN!
WHY IS YOUR SISTER
SO MEAN TO YOU, DUDE?
YEAH, IF SOME SISSY CHICK
TRIED TO KICK MY ASS,
I BE LIKE,
HEY, LISTEN MISSY,
WHY DON'T YOU GO
KNIT ME A SWEATER
BEFORE I SLAP YOU
IN THE FACE?!
WHO SAID THAT?
THIS MUST BE IT.
LOOKS LIKE
NOBODY'S HOME.
GUESS WE SHOULD COME BACK
SOME OTHER TIME.
NO, CARTMAN,
WE'RE GOING IN THERE
AND SPLICING FLUFFY
AND MY ELEPHANT TOGETHER.
IT'S OKAY, FLUFFY,
I WON'T LET THEM HURT YOU.
IT'S JUST
A STUPID PIG.
QUIT BEING
SUCH A BABY.
WELL AT LEAST I DON'T GET
MY ASS KICKED BY A GIRL!
AT LEAST I'M NOT
A LITTLE PIG--
I'M TAKING MY PIG,
AND SCREW YOU GUYS!
I'M GOING HOME!
THIS WHOLE IDEA
IS STUPID ANYWAY!
WHAT THE HELL WOULD YOU KNOW?
YOU FAT SWEATY MONGOLOID.
YOU NEVER GET
HIGHER THAN A "D"!
WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK
TO SAN FRANCISCO
WITH THE REST
OF THE JEWS!
THERE'S NO JEWS IN
SAN FRANCISCO YOU RETARD!
I'LL KICK YOU
IN THE NUTS!
CAN I HELP YOU?
UH, YEAH.
WE WANNA CROSSBREED
AN ELEPHANT WITH A PIG.
BRILLIANT IDEA.
HUGE ELEPHANT-SIZED PIGS.
NO, WE WANNA MAKE LITTLE
POT-BELLIED ELEPHANTS
THAT PEOPLE CAN KEEP
IN THEIR HOUSES AS PETS.
THAT'S AN EVEN
BETTER IDEA.
COME ON IN.
I'M SO PLEASED THAT
YOU CHILDREN ARE INTERESTED
IN GENETIC ENGINEERING.
IT'S OKAY, FLUFFY,
NOBODY'S GONNA HURT YOU.
IT'S THANKS TO THE WONDERS
OF GENETIC ENGINEERING
THAT SOON THERE WILL BE
AN END TO HUNGER,
DISEASE, POLLUTION,
EVEN WAR.
I'VE CREATED THINGS
THAT WILL CHANGE
THE WORLD FOR THE BETTER.
FOR INSTANCE,
HERE'S A MONKEY
WITH FOUR ASSES.
HOW DOES THAT
MAKE THE WORLD BETTER?
AND HERE OF COURSE,
IS MY FOUR-ASSED OSTRICH,
AND MY FOUR-ASSED
MONGOOSE.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING BESIDES
ANIMALS WITH FOUR ASSES?
OH, WELL,
I SUPPOSE SO.
OH, YES,
OVER HERE.
HERE I HAVE RATS
SPLICED WITH DUCKS.
AND GORILLAS SPLICED
WITH MOSQUITOES.
AND HERE I HAVE RABBITS
SPLICED WITH FISH
TO MAKE
LITTLE BUNNY FISH.
THESE BUNNY EARS ARE TIED ON
WITH LITTLE STRINGS!
AND OVER HERE SWISS CHEESE
SPLICED WITH CHALK
AND A BEARD.
WHAT ABOUT OUR
POT-BELLIED ELEPHANT?
OH, WELL,
I'M SORRY, CHILDREN.
BUT PIG AND ELEPHANT DNA
JUST WON'T SPLICE.
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD
THAT SONG BY LOVERBOY?
WHICH SONG
IS THAT?
♪ PIG AND ELEPHANT DNA
JUST WON'T SPLICE ♪
MAYBE I CAN HELP YOU
ADD A FEW ASSES
TO THAT SWINE OF YOURS.
YOU CAN KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF
OF FLUFFY'S ASS!
IT'S AMAZING
WHAT WE CAN DO
WITH A LITTLE
BLOOD SAMPLE THESE DAYS.
OW!
WHAT?
EXCUSE ME.
WAIT, WHAT ARE YOU TAKING
STAN'S BLOOD FOR?
OH, PARDON ME,
I TRIPPED.
COULD I HAVE SOME
HAIR, PLEASE?
WATCH OUT, STAN,
GENETIC ENGINEERS ARE CRAZY!
C'MON, FLUFFY!
THIS QUICHE IS JUST
??
THAT'S
PRETTY FRESH.
OH, I SURE AM
HUNGRY.
'ELLO, GENTLEMEN.
ANY OF YOU BLOKES
KNOW WHAT'S FOR LUNCH?
LUNCHY MUNCHIES, HMM?
GO AWAY, PIP,
NOBODY LIKES YOU!
YEAH, WHAT KIND OF NAME
IS "PIP" ANYWAY?
MY FATHER'S FAMILY NAME
BEING "PHILLIP"
AND MY CHRISTIAN NAME
"PHILLIP"--
WOULD YOU
SHUT THE HELL UP?!
NOBODY GIVES
A RAT'S ASS!
YEAH,
GO AWAY PIP.
RIGHT-O.
FRENCH PEOPLE
PISS ME OFF.
HEY, DUMB ASSES!
YOU MORONS GIVE UP ON YOUR
STUPID SCIENCE FAIR PROJECT?
NO, WE'RE ALREADY
HALFWAY DONE.
THEN ALL YOU'VE GOT
IS A STUPID PIG.
PROBABLY
A GAY PIG, TOO.
IT'S MORE THAN
YOU'VE GOT!
WRONG!
WE ALREADY GOT
OUR CLONE UNDER WAY.
OH, MY GOD,
THEY CLONED A FOOT!
HEY, I'LL
KICK YOUR ASS!
BY FRIDAY WE'RE GONNA CLONE
A WHOLE HUMAN BEING.
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR
STUPID LITTLE PIG.
HELLO THERE,
CHILDREN.
HEY, CHEF.
HOW YOU DOING?
BAD.
WHY?
WE NEED TO GENETICALLY ENGINEER
A PIG AND AN ELEPHANT,
BUT THEIR GENES
WON'T SPLICE.
OF COURSE THEY
WON'T SPLICE, CHILDREN.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER HEARD
THAT SONG BY LOVERBOY?
♪ PIG AND AN ELEPHANT DNA
JUST WON'T-- ♪
A PIG-ELEPHANT?
SAY, THAT'S NOT
A BAD IDEA.
I TOLD YOU GUYS.
IMAGINE A PINT-SIZED
ELEPHANT
THAT YOU COULD
KEEP IN THE HOUSE.
CHILDREN, WE COULD MAKE
A FORTUNE WITH THIS.
YOU HEAR THAT, DUDES?
WE'LL BE RICH!
FORGET ABOUT ALL THAT
GENETIC ENGINEERING HOOSAFUDGE.
IF YOU WANT TO COMBINE
A PIG AND AN ELEPHANT
JUST GET THEM
TO MAKE SWEET LOVE.
I DON'T THINK AN ELEPHANT
WOULD MAKE LOVE TO A PIG.
I DON'T THINK
MY PIG
WOULD WANNA MAKE LOVE
TO THAT STUPID ELEPHANT!
SURE,
THEY WOULD.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
GET 'EM IN THE MOOD.
HOW DO WE
DO THAT?
DO WHAT I DO,
GET 'EM GOOD AND DRUNK.
YOU GUYS WANNA COME OVER
TO MY HOUSE?
WE GOT WORK
TO DO, STAN.
I THINK IT TAKES A WHILE
FOR AN ELEPHANT TO GET DRUNK.
YOU DON'T WANNA COME OVER
FOR A LITTLE BIT?
WHY, YOUR SISTER GONNA
KICK YOUR ASS AGAIN?
SHUT UP,
CARTMAN!
( mumbling )
YEAH, STAN,
SHE'S JUST A GIRL.
YEAH, IF SOME GIRL
TRIED TO KICK MY ASS
I'D BE LIKE, HEY!
WHY DON'T YOU STOP
DRESSING ME UP LIKE A MAILMAN
AND MAKING ME
DANCE FOR YOU
WHILE YOU GO AND SMOKE CRACK
IN YOUR BEDROOM
AND HAVE SEX WITH SOME GUY
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
ON MY DAD'S BED?!
CARTMAN, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?!
I'M JUST SAYING YOU'RE
A LITTLE WUS, THAT'S ALL.
STAN, YOU CAN USE FAMILY LOVE
AS A WEAPON AGAINST SHELLY.
THE NEXT TIME SHE'S GONNA
KICK YOUR ASS,
JUST TELL HER,
"SHELLY, YOU'RE MY SISTER
AND I LOVE YOU."
SICK, DUDE,
SHE'S MY SISTER!
TRY IT.
WE GOTTA GO
GET CARTMAN'S PIG.
NO YOU DON'T GOTTA GET
CARTMAN'S PIG!
YOU LEAVE FLUFFY
OUT OF THIS!
C'MON, KENNY!
KYLE, NO!
NO ELEPHANT IS GONNA
MAKE LOVE TO FLUFFY!
I WILL KICK YOU
IN THE NUTS!
CRAP!
( television )
And now back to
Jesus and pals...
ARE YOU STARING
AT MY NECK BRACE?
NO, I MEAN YES?
I MEAN,
WHAT NECK BRACE?
SHELLY, BEFORE YOU BEAT MY FACE
INTO A BLOODY PULP AGAIN,
I JUST WANT YOU
TO KNOW
THAT YOU'RE MY SISTER
AND I LOVE YOU.
OW!
SOMEDAY I'M GONNA
BE BIGGER THAN YOU
AND YOU'RE GONNA WISH YOU'D
NEVER DONE ANY OF THIS.
YOU'LL NEVER BE BIGGER
THAN ME, STAN.
NEVER!
BEAUTIFUL,
IT'S ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL.
MY SON, I THINK
WE'VE FINALLY DONE IT.
YES, WE HAVE, DAD.
MY VERY OWN
HUMAN CLONE.
HOPE IT'S NOT
A GAY CLONE.
YEAH.
THIS SHOW'S
STUPID.
C'MON, ELEPHANT,
KEEP DRINKING.
I WONDER HOW DRUNK
HE NEEDS TO BE
TO MAKE SWEET LOVE
TO THE PIG.
DAMNIT, THIS IS
NEVER GONNA WORK!
HELLO, CHILDREN.
I THOUGHT
I'D CHECK AND SEE
HOW OUR LITTLE ENTREPRENEURIAL
ADVENTURE IS GOING.
ROTTEN!
THEY'RE BOTH DRUNK
BUT WON'T HAVE SEX!
OH, CHILDREN,
YOU CAN'T STICK A DRUNK PIG
WITH A DRUNK ELEPHANT
AND EXPECT THEM
TO DO THE MATTRESS MAMBO.
YOU NEED TO
SET THE MOOD.
LET ME SHOW YOU BOYS
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
♪ TONIGHT IS RIGHT
FOR LOVE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I WANNA TOUCH YOU
WHERE THE LIGHTS DON'T GO ♪
♪ TONIGHT IS
RIGHT FOR LOVE ♪
♪ LOVE GRAVY ♪
♪ MAKE SPECIAL LOVE
SO SWEET ♪
♪ I WANNA KEEP YOU BURNING
LIKE A DOG IN HEAT ♪
♪ TONIGHT IS
RIGHT FOR LOVE ♪
♪ LOVE GRAVY ♪
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
MR. ELTON JOHN!
♪ OOH, TONIGHT ♪
♪ OH, IT'S RIGHT ♪
♪ OOH, TONIGHT
IS RIGHT FOR LOVE ♪
♪ LOVE GRAVY ♪
THANK YOU, ELTON!
♪ TONIGHT IS
RIGHT FOR LOVE ♪
♪ LOVE GRAVY ♪
HEY LOOK,
IT'S WORKING!
NOW CHILDREN,
GATHER AROUND AND WATCH
THE WONDERS OF LIFE.
THE BEAUTY
OF MOTHER NATURE.
OH, SICK!
FLUFFY!
NOW I KNOW HOW ALL THOSE
WHITE WOMEN MUST'VE FELT.
OUR CREATURE
HAS COME TO FRUITION.
DAD, YOU'RE
THE BEST.
OH, MY GOD!
HE ONLY
HAS ONE ASS!
HE'S OF NO USE TO ME,
I'LL HAVE TO BURN THE ROOM!
OH, NO.
THIS ENTIRE EXPERIMENT
IS TURNING OUT VERY BAD.
ME BAD?
EGATS, HE'S
OUT OF CONTROL.
WE'LL HAVE
TO DESTROY HIM!
BUT HE'S OUR
SCIENCE FAIR PROJECT!
( jibberish )
HE'S TOO
DANGEROUS, SON.
BUT, DAD,
I WANT A HUMAN CLONE!
SON, NO!
SON, YOU'VE MADE
A HORRIBLE MISTAKE.
YOU'VE PUT ALL THE PEOPLE
OF SOUTH PARK IN JEOPARDY!
THEY'RE ALL
STUPID ANYWAY.
C'MON, GUYS,
LET'S GO.
THEY'RE ALL GAY.
AREN'T THEY EVER
GONNA WAKE UP?
OH, THEY WILL.
IT'S GONNA BE
ONE UGLY SIGHT.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THE WONDER OF MOTHER NATURE
WAS A
BEAUTIFUL THING.
WHEN DOES MOTHER NATURE
GO FROM BEAUTIFUL TO UGLY?
USUALLY ABOUT 9:30
IN THE MORNING, CHILDREN.
UH-OH,
HERE WE GO.
THERE'S NOTHING WORSE THAN
GETTING ALL DRUNK
AND WAKING UP THE NEXT MORNING
NEXT TO A PIG!
OR A BIG FAT
ELEPHANT.
HEY, HOW DO WE KNOW
IF SHE'S PREGNANT?
WE MIGHT NOT KNOW
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
COUPLE OF DAYS?
BUT TERRANCE IS GOING TO HAVE
HIS HUMAN CLONE BY TOMORROW.
GOOD JOB,
EINSTEIN!
WHY DON'T WE JUST BUILD
A ROCKET IN THE MEANTIME?
THANK BUDDHA
I FOUND YOU BOYS.
YOU MUST TELL ME, HAVE YOU
SEEN ANYTHING ODD LATELY?
WE SAW AN ELEPHANT
HAVE SEX WITH A PIG.
NO, I SAID ODD.
YOU'RE THAT CRAZY CRACKER
FROM UP ON THE HILL.
SIR, IF MAKING MUTANT ANIMALS
SPLICED WITH HUMANS
IS CRAZY THAN--
UH...
HMM...
NEVERMIND.
THERE'S BEEN A BIT
OF AN INCIDENT AT THE RANCH.
YOU SEE, I'VE CREATED
A LARGE MUTANT CLONE
OF THAT
LITTLE BOY THERE
AND HE'S BROKEN FREE.
( mumbling )
A BIG MUTANT
VERSION OF ME?
IS HE BIGGER
THAN A REGULAR CLONE?
HE'S TERRIBLY
DANGEROUS.
HIS BRAIN
IS IDENTICAL TO YOURS.
I NEED YOU
TO HELP ME FIND HIM.
( crowd screaming )
STAN, ARE YOU WEARING
A DIFFERENT HAT?
HEY!
I KNOW A CERTAIN YOUNG MAN
WHO'S ITCHING FOR DETENTION!
HOW BIG DO YOU
THINK HE IS?
I BET HE WEIGHS
400 POUNDS!
C'MON, STAN, DON'T YOU EVEN KNOW
WHERE YOU WOULD GO?
OH, MY GOD!
It appears that the horrible
destructive creature
is actually eight-year-old
Stan Marsh of South Park.
When asked why he was wreaking
such havoc on his hometown
The little boy replied simply,
"Me Stan...
( jibberish )
Back to you
in the studio.
THANKS, TOM,
POLICE ARE REQUESTING
THAT IF YOU SEE THIS
LITTLE 8-YEAR-OLD BOY
YOU IMMEDIATELY KILL HIM
AND BURN HIS BODY.
THAT'S ALL FOR NOW.
AND NOW BACK TO
"JESUS AND PALS".
THE WAY IS PAVED WITH GOLD
FOR YE WHO SEEK TRUTH.
( jibberish )
JESUS!
OFFICER, MY EVIL GENETIC CLONE
IS DESTROYING THE TOWN!
WE HAVE
TO FIND HIM!
YOU BOYS HAVE BEEN WATCHING
"THE X-FILES" TOO MUCH.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS GENETIC CLONE--!
( gargled speech )
C'MON,
LET'S GO!
THERE YOU ARE!
STANLEY, YOU TORE UP
MY ENTIRE GUN SHOP!
YOU BETTER HAVE
A GOOD EXPLANATION FOR THIS!
IT WASN'T ME UNCLE JIMBO,
IT WAS MY EVIL GENETIC CLONE.
STANLEY, WHAT THE HELL
HAS GOTTEN INTO YOU?!
YOU HAVE GOT SEVERE
LUNCHROOM DUTY, MISTER!
I'M GONNA GO HAVE A WORD
WITH YOUR FATHER, STANLEY!
YOU WAIT 'TILL YOUR FATHER
HEARS ABOUT THIS.
WAIT, STAN,
THERE HE GOES.
STOP!
( jibberish )
HE RECOGNIZES YOU, DUDE.
THAT'S GOOD,
THAT'S GOOD, DUDE.
JUST CALM DOWN.
( jibberish )
WHAT SHOULD
WE DO WITH HIM?
STAN, HOW WOULD YOU
LIKE TO GO HOME
AND MEET
YOUR SISTER?
SHELLY'S THE ONE WITH THE
BIG WIRE COMING OUT OF HER MOUTH
AND A METAL PLATE
ON HER BACK.
WHEN YOU SEE SHELLY,
KICK HER ASS.
SHELLY BAD!
SHELLY VERY BAD!
ME BAD?
NO, SHELLY BAD,
YOU GOOD.
HE'S TEARING UP THE HOUSE,
STOP HIM!
WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU WANT?
( jibberish )
BOYS, BOYS, I'M LUSCIOUSLY
SORRY FOR EVERYTHING.
HEY, THEY GOT OUR CLONE,
HE BELONGS TO US.
NO, SON,
THIS BEAST IS A DISGRACE
TO GENETIC ENGINEERS.
BOYS, I'M SORRY I'VE CAUSED YOU
SUCH INCONVENIENCE.
I TRIED TO PLAY GOD
AND I FAILED.
DADDY, NO...!
ALL I EVER WANTED
WAS TO GENETICALLY ENGINEER
SOMETHING USEFUL,
BUT I FAILED.
PERHAPS WE SHOULDN'T BE TOYING
WITH GOD'S CREATIONS.
PERHAPS WE SHOULD JUST
LEAVE NATURE ALONE
TO ITS SIMPLE
ONE-ASSED SCHEMATICS.
YOU CHEATING BASTARDS,
THIS ISN'T OVER!
JUST WAIT
UNTIL TOMORROW!
OH, MY GOD,
THEY KILLED KENNY!
YOU BASTARD!
MOM AND DAD ARE HOME.
MY HOUSE IS A DISASTER!
YOU GUYS
GOTTA HELP ME.
I AIN'T HELPING CRAP.
I WANNA EAT SOME PIE.
YOU CAN'T JUST
LEAVE ME HERE ALONE!
OH, YEAH?
WATCH ME.
WE HAVE TO FIND OUT IF CARTMAN'S
PIG IS PREGNANT OR NOT.
THANKS A LOT!
OH, BOY, YOU ARE
GONNA GET IT NOW.
IT ISN'T FAIR!
EVERYBODY HATES ME!
THE WHOLE TOWN
WANTS ME KILLED!
MOM AND DAD ARE GONNA
SEND ME AWAY!
I DON'T WANNA BE SENT AWAY,
I WANNA STAY HERE!
STANLEY, WHAT IN GOD'S NAME
HAVE YOU BEEN DOING?!
EVERYBODY IN TOWN IS
UPSET WITH YOU, YOUNG MAN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ARE YOU ON DRUGS?
IT'S NOT
STAN'S FAULT.
HUH?
IT WASN'T STAN.
HE WAS...
HE WAS WITH ME
THE WHOLE TIME.
OH.
WELL STAN, WE'RE SORRY
WE JUMPED TO CONCLUSIONS.
OH, HONEY,
PLEASE FORGIVE US, SON.
SHELLY,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
AND YET YOU'VE DONE
SO MUCH MORE THAN THAT.
TODAY YOU'VE TAUGHT ME
THE MEANING OF FAMILY.
SURE, FAMILIES
DON'T ALWAYS GET ALONG
BUT WHEN THE FORCES OF EVIL
DESCEND UPON US
WE CONQUER THEM
BY STICKING TOGETHER.
OKAY, KYLE,
WE'RE READY TO SEE
YOUR SCIENCE PROJECT.
WELL, OUR PIG HASN'T
GIVEN BIRTH YET,
BUT SHE SHOULD
ANY TIME NOW.
OH, WELL, THEN I GUESS
YOU GET AN "F".
OKAY, TERRANCE, I KNOW
THE CLASS CAN HARDLY WAIT
TO SEE YOUR
SCIENCE FAIR PROJECT.
THANK YOU,
MR. GARRISON.
BOYS, MR. GARRISON,
FELLOW STUDENTS,
FOR OUR
SCIENCE FAIR PROJECT,
BILL FOSSEY AND I
HAVE SPAWNED A CREATURE
GENETICALLY
FAR SUPERIOR TO MAN.
I PRESENT TO YOU...
THE FIVE-ASSED
MONKEY.
OH, MR. HAT,
ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
WAIT, WAIT,
THE PIG JUST GAVE BIRTH!
IT HAD A BABY!
( kid )
WHAT'S IT
LOOK LIKE?
DOES IT LOOK LIKE A PIG,
OR AN ELEPHANT?
HEY, IT KINDA LOOKS
LIKE MR. GARRISON.
OH, GEE, ISN'T THAT
AN AMAZING COINCIDENCE?
WHAT ARE
THE ODDS OF THAT?
HMM...
YOU BOYS
GET FIRST PRIZE.
THAT'LL DO, PIG.
Captions Copyright 1998
COMEDY CENTRAL
A Division of TIME WARNER
ENTERTAINMENT COMPANY, L.P.
Captioned at
HBO COMMUNICATIONS CENTER